[Music]
Don't worry,
Mom, I'll be alright. Papa. It's a small kidney stone
surgery.
Yes, the surgery is small, but there's going to be a big problem.
Papa, you did
n't think about insurance while choosing the hospital. You
scheduled the surgery before I could say anything.
Papa, you know, Mom is
comfortable only with Dr. Desai.
Yes, but Dr. Desai does
n't find the hospital next door comfortable.
Which uncle or aunt sitting here will make it
cashless? If the
hospital's name isn't on the list, it wo
n't be cashless. Don't teach me.
It's good, you keep engrossed in your phone. It's just Papa
who keeps thinking good things about everyone. He keeps
saying, let him talk.
Papa, it's not ICICI Lombard's cashless
facility anyway.
Cashless doesn't happen like this. It will happen now. For the first
time in India, go to any hospital and
get ICICI Lombard's cashless facility.
You just have to inform 24 hours before hospitalization.
I already did it yesterday.
[Music]
What is it, Papa? I learned to think about everyone from
you.
We believe that medical insurance should be free of
complications. That's why for the
first time in India, Anyway Cashless. Get
treated at any hospital and get the same
ICICI Lombard comfort
[Music]